Princeton Ethiopic Manuscripts, late 1600s-1900s: Finding Aid C0776
Manuscripts Division
- Princeton Ethiopic Manuscript No. 41: Miracles of Mary (Tä'ammərä Maryam), Miracles of Jesus (Tä'ammərä Iyassus), 1700s; 41; 199 folios 2 cols., 24 lines. Parchment Codex. Written in black and red ink. Twelve miniatures. No case. Wooden boards with stamped red leather, stitched and open spine 20.5
  - Miracles of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 6v-166r. (Unitid 41)
    - Thirty-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 63v-64r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the merchant from Colossae after being shot in the eye with an arrow by pirates (Budge, Mary, 15).
    - Thirty-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 64v-65v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary restored the sight of a certain blind girl of Bədərman with her breath and milk (Budge, Mary, 16).
    - Thirty-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 65v-66v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary arranged marriages for two poor girls called Martha and Yäwahit (Budge, Mary, 17).
    - Thirty-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 66v-67v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary delivered the soul of the scribe who was writing the book of her miracles (Budge, Mary, 18). Miracle has one folio painted over.
    - Thirty-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 67v-68r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary delivered from prison a certain man called Giyorgis (Budge, Mary, 19).
    - Thirty-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 68rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary protected the elderly priest called Qätir (Budge, Mary, 20).
    - Thirty-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 68v-69v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary sent Saint George to threaten a Qädi (Islamic leader) for imprisoning a Christian (Budge, Mary, 21).
    - Thirty-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 70rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed a man with a stone foot (Budge, Mary, 22).
    - Fortieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 70v-71r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the Bishop Märqorəwos of his leprosy (Budge, Mary, 23).
    - Forty-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 71v-72v. (Unitid 41)
      How a certain rich man hurled a loaf at the head of a beggar and wounded him, and how the Virgin Mary delivered his soul from the devils (Budge, Mary, 86).
    - Forty-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 72v. (Unitid 41)
    - Forty-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 73rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the blind daughter from the city of Qähar.
    - Fragment of a Miracle About a Certain Priest, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 53v. (Unitid 41)
    - Forty-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 73v-74v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the foot of a widow from Harətärom (Budge, Mary, 24).
    - Forty-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 74v-75r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary raised the son of a certain man from Capadocia (not in Budge).
    - Forty-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 75rv. (Unitid 41)
    - Forty-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 75r-76v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the sick deacon by anointing him with her breast milk (not in Budge).
    - Forty-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 76v-77r. (Unitid 41)
    - Forty-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 77r-79r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to the Syrian potter and how he glorified her (Budge, Mary, 35).
    - Fiftieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 79rv. (Unitid 41)
      How Marəqos, King of Rome, fled from his palace for the monastery for the love of the Virgin Mary) (Budge?).
    - Fifty-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 80rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved Qiras the thief.
    - Fifty-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 80v-81v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary commanded a deacon to dig up and rebury in consecrated ground the body of an adulterous deacon from the island of Jericho in the city of Gärisat who was killed by the people) (Budge, Mary, 103, similar to Romances, Cleopatra 9 about Chartres?.
    - Fifty-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 81v-82r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary cut out and sewed a garment for Filatawos, a bishop of the city of Sä'id in Upper Egypt (Budge, Mary, 40).
    - Fifty-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 82r-83r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Paricos when Filatawos refused to give him penance.
    - Fifty-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 83r-84r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved the woman in childbirth from drowning (Budge, Mary, 32; Strelcyn 32.16.31; Bland 2; Romances, Cleopatra 3).
    - Fifty-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 84r-85r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary received the soul of Anəsətasəyos (Budge, Mary, 27).
    - Fifty-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 85rv. (Unitid 41)
      How a certain king from Afəras (France) named Niqodimos recited the Hail Mary his whole life and when he died a tree with Hail Mary written on its leaves sprang from his tomb (Budge, Mary, 38).
    - Fifty-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 85v-86v. (Unitid 41)
    - Fifty-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 86v-87r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to the Bishop to restore a priest called Enədrəyas who knew only the anaphora of the Virgin Mary (Budge, Mary, 102).
    - Sixtieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 87v-88r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved from a great snake Eskənədros the Jew from Jerusalem.
    - Sixty-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 88v-89r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved from death a governor of Ephesus named Armatəyas.
    - Sixty-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 89r-91r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary aided in the delivery of a child to an abbess before the bishop came to enquire into the matter (Budge, Mary, 25; Bland 24 also in Vincent de Beauvais (from 1264 AD). Middle of miracle, one folio, painted over.
    - Sixty-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 91r-92r. (Unitid 41)
      How the icon of the Virgin Mary bowed and responded to the prayer and the bows of a certain monastery's monks (not in Budge).
    - Sixty-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 92r-93r. (Unitid 41)
      How a certain Muslim was converted when he saw oil and Myron from the breasts of the icon of the Virgin Mary.
    - Sixty-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 93r-94r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary helped a young impoverished man and how the church keeper gave his daughter to him.
    - Sixty-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 94r-95r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved the wealthy person from the angels of darkness when he died.
    - Sixty-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 95r-96r. (Unitid 41)
    - Sixty-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 96rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to the widow and commanded her to recite the "Hail Mary" (Budge, Mary, ? ).
    - Sixty-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 97r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to a priest named Yohannəs as a woman with wings like a bird.
    - Seventieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 97v-98v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary interceded and returned a fallen angel to heaven.
    - Seventy-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 98v-99v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved Timothy, a drunken monk, from a lion and a mad dog (Budge, Mary, 37).
    - Seventy-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 99v-100v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved a certain man from drowning when the ship was sinking.
    - Seventy-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 100v-101v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to a man from France (Färasawi) when he denied Christ but kept his devotion to the Virgin Mary.
    - Seventy-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 101v-104r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary recovered a ring stolen by a Muslim and swallowed by the fish for a deacon named Mika' el.
    - Seventy-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 104r-106r. (Unitid 41)
    - Seventy-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 106r-107v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to the French man named Nifon and lead him to the monastic life.
    - Seventy-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 107v-108r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to a monk from the island in Tigris when he couldn't walk and his friends carried him to the church.
    - Seventy-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 108r-109r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary took the shepherd into paradise.
    - Seventy-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 109v-110v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary healed the sister of the thief crucified at the right hand of Jesus Christ.
    - Eightieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 110v-113r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Tewoflos the Archbishop of Alexandria and told him about the events surrounding Jesus's birth when Herod killed the children of Bethlehem.
    - Eighty-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 113r-115vr. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Tewoflos the Archbishop of Alexandria and told him about the flight of the Holy Family into Egypt.
    - Eighty-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 115v-118r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved the monks of Däbrä Qälmon from Arabs.
    - Eighty-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 118v-121r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary recovered the property of the monks of Däbrä Qälmon which had been looted by Berber men.
    - Eighty-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 122rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved Jacob the Short from the hand of the Arabs (incomplete, 122v is painted over).
    - Eighty-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 123r-124v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Qomos (priest) Rafa'el and how she left her handprint on his body.
    - Eighty-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 124v-125v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary punished the Arab when he defied the icon of Saint Mary.
    - Eighty-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 126r-128r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary helped Archbishop [of Alexandria] Gäbrə'el when he tried to send his book, Book of Hawi, to Saint Anthony's Monastery.
    - Eighty-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 128r-129v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved a man named Nəkal of the city of Märg Wäkim from prison and how she led him into martydom.
    - Eighty-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 129v-132r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary guarded the virginity of a priest and nun and how the Virgin Mary revealed their holiness when the rumor circulated about them.
    - Nintieth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 132r-133v. (Unitid 41)
      How the icon of the Virgin Mary healed a woman who suffered from hemorrhage.
    - Ninety-First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 89r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary recovered the stolen book Acts of Barbara and Julia (incomplete, text on fol. 135r painted over).
    - Ninety-Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 135r-136v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary protected the candle oil for the icon from spilling.
    - Ninety-Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 136v-138r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary punished a man who attacked and stole from some monks.
    - Ninety-Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 138r-139r. (Unitid 41)
      How the icon of the Virgin Mary protected Christians in Atrib, Egypt, from the hand of Arabs.
    - Ninety-Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 139r-141r. (Unitid 41)
      How the mother of Yohannəs of Säməbat of lower Egypt received a pious Ethiopian monk and went with him to Jerusalem.
    - Ninety-Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 141r-143r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Afrənəgawi [European man] took the key from the Church of Bethlehem and how the Virgin Mary revealed her power when the Afärəngi was strangled by it.
    - Ninety-Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 143r-144r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to the Muslim and converted him to Christianity and led him to his martyrdom.
    - Ninety-Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 144v-150r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared with archangels, saints, and martyrs at the Däbrä Mətmaq Monastery in Egypt.
    - Ninety-Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 150r-152r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary punished the camel leader of Däbrä Mətmaq Monastery when he stole property from the monastery.
    - One-Hundredth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 152r-153r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Isaac, the monk, and promised to take him to herself after three days.
    - One-Hundredth and First Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 153r-154r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared to Deacon Yohannəs at Däbrä Mətmaq Monastery in the Pillar of Light.
    - One-Hundredth and Second Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 154r-155v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary filled the well at Däbrä Mətmaq Monastery with water.
    - One-Hundredth and Third Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 155v-156r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary appeared with saints who are buried at the monastery of Asqetəs.
    - One-Hundredth and Fourth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 156rv. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary helped a certain monk from the monastery of Asqetəs when he pleaded with the icon of the Virgin Mary to save him from demons.
    - One-Hundredth and Fifth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 157r-158r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary turned on the lamp in the City of Gaza.
    - One-Hundredth and Sixth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 158v-161r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved a man called Joseph when he fell into a well.
    - One-Hundredth and Seventh Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 161r-162r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved the miner when the mine collapsed in the city of Aragon in Capadocia (Budge, Mary,78).
    - One-Hundredth and Eighth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 163r-164v. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved the cupbearer of the king of France (Afransa) when he was tricked into offending the king.
    - One-Hundredth and Ninth Miracle of Mary, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 164v-166r. (Unitid 41)
      How the Virgin Mary saved a man when he denied Christ after Satan promised him great wealth.
  - Miracles of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-196v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Tenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
      How Judas Iscariot killed himself and how the Jewish leader took the money and gave it to the soldiers who guarded the tomb of Jesus Christ.
    - One-Hundredth and Eleventh Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Twelfth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Thirteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Fourteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Fifteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Sixteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Seventeenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Eighteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Nineteenth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Twentieth Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Twenty-First Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 166v-167v. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Twenty-Second Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 191v-194r. (Unitid 41)
    - One-Hundredth and Twenty-Third Miracle of Jesus, 1700s; multiple folios; Located on folio 194v-196v. (Unitid 41)
      How Jesus Christ sent his disciples to bring the donkey and its foal and entered into Jerusalem.
- Princeton Ethiopic Manuscript No. 42: The Cycle of Kings (Awədä Nägäśət), Collection of Divination Texts, 1788-1800; 42; 126 folios 1 col. [fols. 1-30, 117-126]; 2 columns [fols. 31-116]; lines vary throughout. Parchment Codex. Written in black and red ink. Two miniatures. Leather carrying case with strap. Wooden boards, broken lower board, stitched and open spine. Fols. 82r-85v: Inserted four-folio quire of tiny size: 6 cm x 7.5 cm. 13.5 x 18 cm (Unitid 42)
  Illustrations: Fols. 34v-35v: Fortune-telling charts with birthdates and letters of names.
  Illustrations: Fols. 36rv: Magical pictures representing the four quarters of the heavens.
  Illustrations: Fols. 37r-44v: Sixteen magical circles.
  Illustrations: Fols. 72v-73r: Talismanic symbol.
  Fol. 114v: Note is made of the Ethiopian kings from the first king of the Solomonic dynasty, Yəkuno Amlak (r. 1270-1285), through King Takla Haymanot (r. 1788- 89) and "up to now," King Tekle Giyorgis, who ruled off and on from 1788 to 1800 AD.
  According to Aethiopica Encyclopedia (p. 402), "The Cycle of the Kings" consists of "circular tables dealing with divination and fortune-telling." The "basis of the fortune-telling is 16 sixteen-sector schemes named after lakes or rivers ... in Ethiopia... The schemes always have the same division, there are only differences in the lettering (in alphabetical order) of the segments. Each scheme and its segments find their explanation (i.e. the answer to the question posed) in corresponding texts following the tables."
  Regarding previous cataloging of Cycle of the Kings, B.Turaev, Efiopskiya rukopisi v S. Peterburge, Sanktpeterburg 1906 III, 11, 23, 46; Strelcyn (Graule) 390, 391, 405, 641, 650; E. Ullendorff and Stephen G. Wright, Catalogue of Ethiopian manuscripts in the Cambridge University Library, Cambridge, 1961. LVII; S. Strelcyn Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts of the Wellcome Institute of the History of Medicine in London. Bulletin of the School of Oriental and African Studies, Vol.xxxv(1972), pp.27-54 XVII, For further information, see C.Conti Rossini " Lo 'Awda nagast scritto divinatorio etiopico" RSE, 1941,127-45; Marcel Griaule, Notes sur l'arithmomancie éthiopi éthiopienne enne" Journal de l Societe des Africanistes 4, 1934, 25-31 Strelcyn 98, Encyclopedia Aethiopica vol. 1, pp.402; Zä-Mänfäs Qəddus Abrəha Hatäta Mänafəst ... Wä-Awdä Nägäśt, Asmara, 1949 E.C.
  - Magical Prescription against Evil Eye, Epilepsy, Thieves, and Successful Delivery, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 1r-3v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prescription (Upside Down) to Aid Conceiving a Child, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 2v. (Unitid 42)
  - Hasab (calculations?) Concerning the Sick Person, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 4r. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer to Draw a Woman Back After She Went With Another Man, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 4v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer to Cause the Drowning of Demons, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 5r. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer for Gaining Respect and Favor, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 5v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer to Cause the Binding of Demons, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 6r. (Unitid 42)
  - Prayer for Protecting Suckling Infants, Containing the Legend of Susenyos, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 6r-8v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prescription and Prayer for Protection from Thieves and Bandits, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 9r. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer to Make It Impossible for Other Men to Approach One's Woman, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 9v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prescription against Typhoid, Cancer, and Leprosy, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 9v-10v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer for Gaining Love and Respect from Kings and Officials and People Everywhere, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 11r. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer for Protection of Property, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 11v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prescription against Stroke, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 12r. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer for Protection, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 12v. (Unitid 42)
  - Magical Prayer Using Archangel Michael's Magical Names (Asmat), 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 13r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning the Fate of a Man Thrown Into Prison, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 13r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning (Unidentified, Illegible), 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 13r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Power, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 13v-14r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Age, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 14r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Deceit, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 14r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Journeys, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 14v. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning the Coming of Sickness and Death, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 14v-15r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning the Coming of Enemies, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 15r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Long-Distance Business, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 15r. (Unitid 42)
  - Anqäs Concerning Daily Subsistence, 1788-1800; multiple folios; Located on folio 15rv. (Unitid 42)